# Manali Dhananjay Bhamare (1) Featured



Software Engineer, Seeking assignments as a Java Developer, Web Development, Application Development, Selenium Testing, Agile/Scrum Methodology, J2EE JavaScript, Hibernet, Cloud Computing



Current Location: Pune Total Experience: 3 Year(s) 3 Month(s)

Pref. Location: Pune Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming / Highest Degree: PG Diploma [cloud computing]

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Single/unmarried

Key Skills: junit,core java,java j2ee developer,jdbc,myeclipse,netbeans,servlets,cloud computing,agile/scrum

methodology,java,javascript,mysql,clear quest,c#,Spring Mvc,Hibernate,IOC,Spring,Aop,Maven

Verified: Email - id Phone Number |

Last Active: 1-Dec-20 Last Modified: 1-Dec-20

# Summary

Working Experience as a Software Engineer for IBM Watson Health, Curam at Dublin, Ireland. Post Graduate Diploma in Cloud Computing (National College of Ireland). Bachelors in Computer Science (MIT, Pune). Interested in securing role as a Software developer

# Work Experience

### Veritas Client Location as VSOC Analyst

Jun 2018 to Aug 2019

Level 1 & Level 2 Security Analysis.

- Monitoring and analysis for Cyber Security Incidents.
- Source code violations ticketing and level 1 analysis.
- General malware detection and awareness.
- **GDPR** Monitoring
- Torrent Monitoring.
- Level 1 analysis and response for phishing or spam emails.
- Tools worked on:
- Service Now
- Splunk

#### GB controls and Services as Software Developer

Jun 2017 to Apr 2018

PROJECT 1: Online Software Update for Pump Control System.

Description: Desktop based application for GSM based online monitoring for irrigation system that would displaying binary data of controller on the server which would control the irrigation system panel for the clients where the control panels are installed

Language: C#.Net, Java, HTML, CSS

Database: MYSQL

Maintenance and Support for Existing Java based Projects.

#### IBM Watson Health as Software Engineer

Nov 2015 to Dec 2016

1 year Working Experience as a Software Engineer in IBM

Working for a project on Social Assistance operated by Watson Health.

Worked on multiple domains in Curam solutions:

SPM

Accessibility

Dynamic Evidence

Birt Charts

BIApp

Member Notes

Following the Agile/Scrum Process, Test Driven Development, and Peer Reviewing for improved coding Standards, MVC architecture.

Experience in operating Jenkins builds using Ant script.

Working on Apache Tomcat Server, JAWS for accessibility, Jira, Rational Team Concert, Clearcase, Clear Quest.

Understanding of the security standards required for developing websites

Ability to work independently as well as in Group projects

Reference: Ronan Bowers (Ronan.Bowers@ie.ibm.com) - Project Manager

#### **Education**

UG: B.Sc (Computers) from MIT in 2014

PG: PG Diploma (cloud computing) from national college of ireland in 2015

Other Qualifications/Certifications/Programs:

Cyberark Certification

## IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
Java, JavaScript, HTML, MYSQL	8	2016	2 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
XML, JSON		2016	1 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
Clear Case, Clear Quest,SOAP and RESTful			
Jenkins builds.			0 Year(s) 0 Month(s)
SALESFORCE		0	0 Year(s) 1 Month(s)
APEX		0	0 Year(s) 1 Month(s)

# Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Expert			
Marathi	Expert			
Hindi	Expert			

## **Affirmative Action**

Category: OBC - Creamy
Physically Challenged: No

## **Work Authorization**

Countries: India

Job Type: Permanent

Employment Status: Full time